NATALIA W KUKULA

Email: kukula@yahoo.com
Github: github.com/nataliakukula
Phone: 312-709-6145
LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/nataliakukula

Chicago, IL 60613 **Portfolio:** <u>nataliakukula.github.io/professional-portfolio</u>

Web Developer with an educational background in public relations and media marketing, experience in hospitality and advertising, which led to gaining high level communication skills, detail-orientedness, entrepreneurial interest towards human-centered design.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Node.Js, mySQL, mongoDB, Express, Handlebars, Bootstrap, jQuery

APPLICATIONS BUILT

Trivia Chicago - Front End Application

- Utilizes dynamic Javascript to allow users answer questions and keep track of their answers
- Built with: HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap, Javascript, jQuery
- Website: <u>nataliakukula.github.io/TriviaGame</u>

LIRI - Back End Application

- Liri bot (a language interpretation and recognition interface) makes API calls to render data in the CLI
- Built with: Node.Js, Git Bash, Javascript, APIs, NPM packages, JSON
- Link: github.com/nataliakukula/liri-node-app

Know Your Alderman - Collaborative Project

- App provides information on Chicago aldermen (educating and informing about local governments)
- Built with: HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Javascript, jQuery, AJAX, Firebase, APIs
- Website: kaylaverheyen.github.io/know_your_alderman

EDUCATION

Certificate - Full Stack Web Development Bootcamp

Northwestern University, Chicago, IL

Master's Degree - Journalism, Public Relations and Media Marketing University of Warsaw, Warsaw, Poland

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Guest Experience Manager

Ginosi Apartels, Chicago, Illinois, US. March 2017 – August 2018

- Follow policy while multi-tasking through company's software.
- Support headquarters to fulfill customer service requests.
- Provide staff training, inspect their work, hire team members per human resources' request.
- Report any guest, staff, apartment, software issues to line manager daily.
- Create processes and documentation to make restocking inventory levels (PAR) more efficient.

Guest Service Host

Ivy Boutique Hotel, Chicago, Illinois, US. February 2017 – July 2018

- Register and process guests to their assigned rooms and handle payments.
- Accommodate guest requests and provide concierge assistance.
- Communicate with hotel staff on the status of guest rooms.
- Multi-task through different computer systems such as InnRoad, Saflok, HelloShift etc.
- Make reservations, upselling guest rooms and promote hotel services.

Front Desk Manager

Dream Hostel Warsaw, Dream Hostels LTD., Warsaw, Poland May 2016 – January 2017

- Work on the opening team to startup a new chain hostel and create efficient processes.
- Hiring, training, team building, scheduling, evaluating, supervising staff and hostel events.
- Assist with operations and cooperate with the central office to manage guest reservations.
- Focus on customer satisfaction while upholding hostel standards.
- Help achieve Trip Advisor's star of excellence of 2016 within 8 months of operating and become the best hostel in Warsaw.

Advertising Representative

Tribune Publishing, Chicago, Illinois, USA January 2015 – January 2016

- Fulfill customer's requests for over 35 different publications such as the Chicago Tribune.
- Multi-task through different computer systems and applications such as Adit, SharePoint and Microsoft Office.
- Aid customers in locating ads through <u>www.legacv.com</u> and MerlinOne E-sheets.
- Utilize soft sale techniques to aid customers in finding the correct products.
- Give a 100% to achieve largest revenue on the team and receive an award for making almost \$250,000 in quarter II.